Amanda Steele Show today goes to a Rikers Island detainee who did what a lot of people in Manhattan
been wanting to do. Daniel Oheb Shalom, who is known as one of the worst landlords in New York
City. What a title to have. He got punched in the face at Rikers Island recently. So he's there
because he failed to perform hundreds of court-ordered repairs on his Manhattan properties.
Let me correct my language. It's not that they don't like him. It's that he is harmful to people's
lives. That's why he got punched in the face. And I know there were definitely people who heard this
and were like, yeah! Today's lockdown goes to people who are doing too much with this phone.
A viral TikTok video showed a woman recording Keith Murray of hip-hop group The Deaf Squad is the most
beautiful thing in this world. Mr. Magical Mythical. Okay. He has had, you know, reports of mental
illness in the past and he appeared to be distressed and, you know, just down bad outside
of a motel. And this woman was doing this. Do you want money? You really Keith Murray? Can you sing
something? Rap something? You want $20? So rap. Yo, stop it. Just stop it. That is so degrading. That
like really like made me upset just now. When you look at someone like Keith Murray and in her instance,
she's looking at him like, well, he's a celebrity so he doesn't deserve basic respect.
I wish compassion was on the same sale rack as audacity because we'd be in a whole different
situation in our society.